# Jelena Vuckovic



Hardworking new challenges lover with excellent attendance and punctuality records and can work equally well alone or as part of a team.

With 11 years of diverse and progressive experience in customer relations, sales and administrative affairs.

#### **Education**

September 2010 – June 2011

- Degree of Specialist Faculty of Tourism and Hotel Management, Kotor Montenegro - Direction Hotel Management September 2005 – June 2008
- Bachelor Degree in Business Management Faculty for Business Management,

University of Montenegro, Podgorica Montenegro September 2001 – June 2005

Gymnasium, general direction - High School "Danilo Kis", Budva Montenegro - June 2001

Work experience

June 2019 – December 2020

#### Volume Licensing Agent • Majorel, Münster Germany

- Support for business customers,
- Daily communication via email and phone;
- Investigating the issues and providing the solutions in various Microsoft programs;
- Creating the best possible support in daily communication.

April 2017 – April 2019

### CRM Advisor • BlueLink International CZ SRO, Prague Czech Republic

- Communication with passengers via phone, e-mail and Social media channels (Facebook, What's App, Twitter);
- Assisted passengers with creating flight bookings, changing existing reservations;
- Complex before/after flight care including solving complaints about general issues, lost luggage, deny boarding, missing flights, flight cancellation or delay;
- One of job tasks included training chat robotic bots;
- My main achievement was to help passengers to have a trouble-free flight and a Perfect after-flight care and keep client's confidence;
- Worked with programs and applications of the airline company: Sky Speed, TIP, VPN, Citrix, ROD, Nice, Shift management, Excel tables;
- Learned and achieved skills for problem solving, customer service and how to approach so many different persons with understanding the equal importance of their problems.



**Contact** 

**Muenster Germany** 

01523 777 92 57

jeckavucko@gmail.com

Skills

Stress tolerance

Teamwork & leadership Time management & prioritization

Problem solving & multitasking Negotiation and influence Drive for results Strong communication

Adaptability & confidentiality Quick learner and new challenges lover Impeccable organizational skills Strong work ethic

Conflict resolution MC Office Excel, Word, Power point Driver's license - category B
Yoga and meditation practitioner

. . . . . . .

## Jelena Vuckovic

December 2016 - March 2017

#### Sales executive • BIS GROUP SRO, Prague Czech Republic

- Daily calls to head of management in various types of companies, depending on the conferences subject;
- Developed my searching skills, how to choose the right person to approach between different employee types.

January 2012 - October 2016

## Adviser for clients • Sava Montenegro Insurance LTD, Budva Montenegro

- Advised clients on motor, home, health and commercial insurance products;
- Responded quickly to customer inquiries about their insurance policies;
- Established client's insurance needs by asking them relevant questions, educated customers on financial payment options and maintain accurate and relevant customer administrative records;
- Managing appointments and calendar;
- Organized meetings with prospective clients and business owners;
- Increased my portfolio by 100 % in the first year and managed to become the best seller in my branch office in short period;
- Achieved to recognize clients need, managed to advise them accordingly and maintained the portfolio increasing constantly.

April 2011 - November 2011

#### Office Administrator • Trenkwalder LTD, Budva Montenegro

- Oversee office administration to ensure operations run smoothly;
- Filled out applications for employment foreigners in Montenegro, sorted and prepared documentation;
- Very active daily conversation with international clients as well as cooperation with numerous companies from all Montenegrin cities.

June 2008 - October 2010

#### Manager Assistant • MC Marina Budva LTD, Budva Montenegro

- Coordinated and participated in contract negotiations; preparing/editing contract agreements;
- Answer any inquiries customers may have within a short time-span;
- Created reservations, conclusion of contract with clients, finished regular business activities in cooperation with banks and other financial and accounting institutions;
- Daily communication with domestic and international clients/building long-term business relationships;
- Organized monthly schedules of all vessels in marina, yachts and sailing boats on the berths at the docks according to the reservations and space needed. It was very challenging but in cooperation with colleagues we managed to make each client well cared and satisfied;
- Office administration and organization for 20 40 employees including maintaining the database of incoming correspondence and ensuring that follow-up action is taken and that deadlines are met.



#### Languages

Croatian/Serbian/Montenegrin - native

English – proficiency

#### **Core Competencies**

Office Management
Client Relations Building
Sales
Clients advisor
Business Correspondence
Case Analysis
Records Management
Coordinating & scheduling